<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IIITMStars</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">IIITMANIPUR</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">t.raman@iiitmanipur.ac.in</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_aboutiiitm">About IIITM</string>
    <string name="menu_academics">Academics</string>
    <string name="menu_department">Department</string>
    <string name="menu_people">People</string>
    <string name="menu_tnp">TnP</string>
    <string name="menu_info">Info</string>
    <string name="menu_contactus">Contact Us</string>

    <string name="bottom_home_text">Home</string>
    <string name="bottom_notification_text">Notification</string>
    <string name="bottom_ac_text">Notice</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="about_us_one">Indian Institute of Information Technology Senapati,
        Manipur (IIITM) is an institution under MHRD, Govt. of India. IIIT Senapati,
        Manipur was established in 2015 in order to develop Manipur as preferred
        destination for Information Technology (IT) related manpower and industry.</string>
    <string name="about_us_two">This shall enable Manipur to gear up for providing
         IT related services as well as high-quality Research and Development in IT.</string>
    <string name="about_us_three"> IIIT Senapati, Manipur offers B.Tech programmes in two disciplines,
         Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) and Electronics and Communication
         Engineering (ECE) from its transit campus located at Mantripukhri,
        Opposite of Software Technology Park, Near CRPF Camp in Imphal.</string>
    <string name="about_us_four">
         The campus holds classrooms, labs, faculty rooms, seminar hall,
        play ground, faculty quarters, guest house and administrative offices.</string>
    <string name="about_us_five">
         IIIT Senapati, Manipur permanent campus will come up at Ningthoupham
         village, Mayangkhang, Senapati district of Manipur.</string>
    <string name="about_us_six">IIIT Senapati, Manipur is one of the 20 IIITs set up
        by the Central Govt. in PPP mode. A Bill (Act of Parliament) to declare all
        the PPP-IIITs (including IIIT Senapati, Manipur) as Institutes of National
        Importance has been placed before the Lok Sabha.</string>
    <string name="about_us_seven">IIIT Senapati, Manipur strives to be attentive to
        academic needs of every student. Classes are conveniently scheduled between
        8 A.M. to 4:30 P. M. Every class room is well maintained and has projection
        facilities. An Institute-wide wi-fi system provides Internet access throughout
        the Institute.</string>
    <string name="about_us_eight">IIIT Senapati, Manipur is mentored by IIT Guwahati,
        Interim Director Prof. Amarendra Kumar Das is actively working and the transit
        complex is provided with all required infrastructure for overall development of
        the institute. IIIT Senapati, Manipur is also looking for private/industry partner
        for the institute.</string>
    <string name="about_us_nine">It is also mandated to start Design and Manufacturing disciplines
        to positively contribute to Govt. of India mission of Act East and creating manufacturing
        hub in South East Asia. To contribute to Human Resource development of its neighboring
        countries, IIIT Senapati, Manipur will be looking for opportunities to spread IT education
        to Myanmar by providing required facilities to students of that country to study in IIIT
        Senapati, Manipur through bi-lateral agreements.</string>


    <string name="ppp_for_iiitm_one">Partner in PPP for IIIT Senapati, Manipur</string>
    <string name="ppp_for_iiitm_two">Manipur is not having any significant presence of
        any big corporate house or MNC to be partner in IIIT Senapati, Manipur in PPP mode.
        Manipur State IT SEZ Deevelopment Company (MIPDCO) has taken the lead to Industry
        partner in this effort so that IIIT Senapati, Manipur can be realized. IIIT Senapati,
        Manipur acknowledge Manipur Development Society for being the initial partner</string>
    <string name="ppp_for_iiitm_three">1. Industry Partner: Representative of Manipur State IT
        SEZ Deevelopment Company (MIPDCO)</string>
    <string name="ppp_for_iiitm_four">2. Implementing Agency: Manipur State IT Society (MSITS)</string>
    <string name="ppp_for_iiitm_five">3. Working Agency: State PWD</string>


    <string name="mission_and_vision_one">Mission</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_two">The IIIT Senapati, Manipur undertakes the mission to
        provide technical education by offering state-of-the-art undergraduate, postgraduate and
        doctoral programmes with international standards of excellence and with emphasis on research
        to undertake collaborative projects which offer opportunities for long-term interaction with
        academia and Information Technology (IT) industry as well as technology development in the area
        of national importance</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_three">Vision</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_four">To contribute to India and the World through excellence in
        Information Technology in general; to build leaders and entrepreneurs through transformative and
        Innovative Education in the context of socio-economic relevance to the North East of India in
        particular; to serve as a valuable resource for industry and society; and remain a source of
        pride for all Indians.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_five">Manipur, being projected as a Gateway to South East Asia under
        the Look East Policy of the Government of India, IIIT Senapati, Manipur will be looking for
        opportunities to spread IT education and to contribute to Human Resource development in its
        neighboring countries.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_six">IIIT Senapati, Manipur has a vision of establishing itself
        as an Institution of excellence in Cyber Security, Cyber Crime and Forensic so that human resource
        from IIIT Senapati, Manipur will be prepared to face this growing global threat. It also envisages
        itself for achieving excellence in application of robotics facilitating human life to overcome
        congenital as well as acquired disabilities.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_seven">Objectives</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_eight">IIIT Senapati, Manipur has been set up as an institute of
        international standard for offering UG (B.Tech.), PG (M.Tech.) and Ph.D. degree with a unique
        model of partnership of the Govt. of India in joint partnership with State Government of Manipur
        and industry partners.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_nine">To provide best-in-class human resources to the growing electronics,
        manufacturing and design and IT software and services industry in India as well as technology development
        in the area of national importance such as e-Governance in the medium terms.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_ten">The IIIT Senapati, Manipur also aims in foster research and development
        in advanced engineering and applied sciences in M.Tech. and Ph.D. levels.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_eleven">To have a strong industry interface to harness the multi-dimensional
        facets of IT, electronics and design in various domains.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_twelve">To increase the student capacity to meet the growing demands for industry
        leaders from domestic and international Markets.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_thirteen">To achieve international character by having provision for intake of a
        certain percentage of foreign students right from graduation level, especially from the South East Asian and
        SAARC countries.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_fourteen">To provide mechanism for exchange of faculty with similar institutions
        of international repute.</string>
    <string name="mission_and_vision_fifteen">To improve the quality of life of people in general and socio economic
        environment of North East India region in particular as outreach activity.</string>


    <string name="facilities_one">Facilities</string>
    <string name="facilities_two">IIIT Senapati, Manipur is operating at present from its Transit Campus at Mantripukhri,
        Imphal. Although institute is in a transit campus, it has all facilities required for an institute of national
        importance such as state of the art lab, class rooms, wifi connected campus, Library, Auditorium, Hostels,
        faculty residences within the campus, play ground etc.</string>


    <string name="visior_info_one">Visitors Info</string>
    <string name="visior_info_two">Manipur is a beautiful place, close to nature and stable weather conditions all the
        time. The maximum temperature in the summer months is 32째C (90째F). In winter the temperature often falls below 0째C
        (32째F), bringing frost.</string>
    <string name="visior_info_three">By Air</string>
    <string name="visior_info_four">IIIT Senapati, Manipur transit campus is within Imphal town on Imphal Kohima Road,
        NH 2 and approximately 10 Km from Tulihal Airport in Imphal. The campus is very secure, near new
        building and opposite of Manipur Information Technology Park. Taxis (Virgo Cab service and Lamjingba Cab service),
        Auto rickshaws are readily available from the airport to the institute. Imphal, capital of Manipur is well connected
        by air from various places of India and airlines operate daily flights to and from Imphal like Air India, Indigo,
        Jet Airways, Air Asia are operating flights to Imphal either via Kolkata or Guwahati depending on origination of
        the flights.</string>
    <string name="visior_info_five">By Rail</string>
    <string name="visior_info_six">Rail route is yet to reach Imphal, but expected to reach Tupul near Imphal by 2018.
        At present nearest Rail head is at Dimapur and there are bus services to Imphal from Dimapur.</string>
    <string name="visior_info_seven">By Bus</string>
    <string name="visior_info_eight">IIIT Senapati, Manipur transit campus is within Imphal town on Imphal Kohima Road,
        NH 2. Bus services from the nearest railway station Dimapur and Guwahati are available. It takes around
        7-8 hours from ISBT, Dimapur and 12-15 hours from ISBT, Guwahati depending upon type of buses.</string>
    <string name="visior_info_nine">IIIT Senapati, Manipur paternity started in 2015 with two B Tech programs
        (Computer Science and Engineering and Electronics and Communication Engineering). IIIT Senapati, Manipur
        have good enough faculties/technical staff for respective departments/courses and all are well qualified
        with PhD/MTech degree. IIIT Senapati, Manipur have all the facilities within the campus, academic building
        (Class rooms, ECE Labs, Computer Center, Library and Study room), admin building, auditorium, faculty quarters,
        guest house, girls hostel, three hostels for boys with well-equipped dining hall, sports ground (football and cricket),
        WiFi facility and other sports facilities including open gym.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_people">People</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Student</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">faculty</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">technical Staff</string>
</resources>
